

CHRISTIAN PAUL CAMENTO

Web Developer

About Me

Im a web developer with experience in web development and currently working in real estate industry since 2019 up to now. I am a hard working, honest individual and always willing to learn new skills.

- 09239458004
- cpcamento@gmail.com
- Pasak Pardo Cebu City

Language

- Cebuano
- English (basic)
- Filipino

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

- PHP
- HTML
- CSS/SCSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- JSON
- API
- JQUERY
- LARAVEL
- CODEIGNITER
- WORDPRESS

Experience

Vestahomes Commercial Inc. - Real Estate Industry Web Developer 2019 - Present

Developed and Designed Website using laravel | wordpress

Deploy website in hosting

Developed website | system from scratch

Create update and maintain all website

Create themes and plugins

Coolab Digital Marketing - IT Industry Fullstack Developer - (FREELANCER) Feb 2022 - Dec 2022

Developed Laravel Application and Wordpress Plugin

Deploy Application in hosting

Maintain application and plugin

Make website responsive

Static Data Hosting OJT | Intern 2018 - 2019

Designed wordpress website

Create Update and Maintain Website

Education

University of Cebu (Main Campus)

Bachelor of Science Information Technology

Don Vicente Rama Memorial National High School

Taloot Central Elementary School